Um, there's a meeting that's just going
wrong. OK, I'll just join you soon.
Right. OK, got that. Thanks.
One question.
Dave just give a shout out
when you feel we have the
right people. I see for shades
here. So to my agenda was
SER today. Yep. And what I'd
like to cover for that is, um.
Again, I I would I would I would
advise or suggest if we could just start
from the top from me to make sure
when I update my project plan, I'd like
to evaluate where we are for SER the
instance configuration setup and then
understand from the.
TD team past that, what you're
what you're what you're sort of
strategy is for testing and preparing
for cutover for the application
environment. Does that make sense?
So I would say in a in a simple sense,
just make sure that we have the
requirements captured for the plan.
No, it's done. That's great. No, that's
for you Every it's for us. It's for
you. It's it's easy bank.
Right. I
was saying to others asking Daniel and
Jet if they're OK with you can start this
on Sarah without them. And then the only
the only other item I had on the agenda
if time permits, if I could ask a
question, Dave for you to follow up with
the TD team is the. How
do we, how do we keep the, the
hardware, the the design and the hardware
deployment? I know we were talking about
having that discussion around that in
June. If we can add that to an
agenda. So when we bring it to Dan,
my Dan, Dan wheel is attention. We say,
hey here, here's the hardware refresh.
This is the design we talked about way
back in April. This is the one we
want to certify and we talked about that
hardware replacement strategy or planning
session and what you're going to be
asking of Dan Wheeler for that setup and
and certification. All right. So yeah,
that sounds good. Your object and
yeah, Danielle and everyone here. OK, so
because they're, they're, they're gonna
have the provision then. So yeah, so
they're supposed to be racked and stacked
by this weekend. Yeah.
Almost finished already. So yeah, so and
again, I don't want to steal this like I
don't want to go off. Let's focus on SER
today. We're ready to go and then as long
as we we plan accordingly and be
considered to all our team for going
forward for that, for that discussion
around the hardware replacement, OK. All
right, sounds good.
Alright, SER is secure e-mail relay.
It is essentially a system by
proof point that is designed to
take transaction slash something like.
Sorry, just getting a little bit
of feedback there. It's a system
that is designed to take transactional
AKA. Automated traffic and send it
outbound and legitimize it through the
use of two dedicated IP addresses where
you can update your SPF records or
it can apply a DKIM signature on
that outbound e-mail so that you can
do either or you can do both.
Essentially you could be 100%. Mark
compliant with those automated
transactional outbound emails.
And do feel free to pause me, ask me to
stop if you have any questions at all
during the course of this.
So SER is essentially 2 separate
layers. We have what is called
the authentication layer. That is a
method where we will take a
username and password and send emails
up to. Another way of calling
it is the SCR cloud. There's
some and that username is
identified as your organization specific
meaning because it is username
and password. And further we
can restrict it via IP
address if you want. We
identify it as de facto
TD banks outbound e-mail. We
will then route that to a
dedicated outbound TD Bank SER cluster
and that cluster is is what
has your dedicated IP addresses, your
two SER specific IP addresses and
where we can do that DKIM
signing. Furthermore, we can apply
additional filtering or different.
Routing options there as well and
that system will eventually have your
proof point, DLP and encryption services
as well. So any questions with
that then?
Is the authentication part going to be
multiple accounts or just expected to be
one account And we provide based on IP
at that point or as many accounts as
you need. So those accounts are called
relay users. And when we dive into the
product, we can absolutely do that in
just a little bit. Right now, whatever
you want here when we dive into
the product, we can create a sample
relay user and we can look at
all of the properties that individual
relay user has and then you can
build towards the individual user, right
or correct?In
fact, we can apply tags or parameters
to those relay users and those tags
can be assigned to individual application
owners for the purpose of data tracking
and eventually in the product, I believe
sometime during Q3 here, you will be
able to use those tags to allow
the. Application owners to modify their
relay users correctly. Not required, but
it's a nice option to have.
The big consideration typically with most
of the people I've worked with
on SER is well, we have
lots of applications that can't handle
SMTP authentication, IE they are very
simple e-mail sending systems only and
they don't know how to apply.
The username and password. In that case,
we are going to need an optional
third layer, or if you're looking at
it from a pipeline standpoint, a first
layer where we can send e-mail to
that first layer. In this case, we're
on Prem MPA's and then those on
Prem MTA's. Can send the e-mail to
the SER cloud layer which is where
we are giving it the username and
password to identify that traffic as
clearly TD banks traffic.
Any questions with that?
No. But when an application is assigned
to a username and password, is there
a limitation like you know how many
emails per day, how many emails per
hour and things like that? Just the
overall limitation by the system.
However, you as SER administrators are
going to apply your organizational
limitations. That you want if if
necessary. So on each individual relay
user you can set a cap of
number of messages, number of bytes, that
sort of thing.
OK. So
on the first layer, let's say that
they can't authenticate. Will we be using
the?Some people people profiler
to do that with the MTH. Yes, and
those MTA's are going to be separate
proof point clusters.
Do any of you have
access to the r.proofpoint.com admin
console?Yes, you too.
If I could get somebody to log into that
and share out their screen, I would like
to walk through the relay users and the
other areas of that admin console.
OK. I'll let me log in first.
Excellent. Thank you. Took care of that.
Look here.
Alright, I see you started screen
sharing. Thank you for that.
No problem. Rustic.
Alright.
And look at that single sign on. It is
telling you that your organization has
not given you access to that. Yeah, it
was working, but they changed that. So
I've got to log into my pad VDI to
make that work one second. OK, Yeah, not
a problem.
Her point is a security company and
we don't we don't begrudge organizations
extra security features.
Let's try again.
So.
Anybody else has access to
SCR until I fix my
path?Check do
you have access to SCR? I could try if
you want. Ohh good 'cause I was going to
say, not that I want to admit to it.
I'll fix this soon, I'll let you
guys know.
Hey.
Where am I here?
Chemistry.
OK. Just wanted to make sure.
All right, fantastic. So we are in
SER. I would recommend that we expand
that left hand side menu so that
it stays open and. To all see what
those options are. Perfect, Thank you. So
at the very top, we have the reporting
feature, not much use. So we actually
have traffic going through here. Notice
the no data available, we haven't sent
anything through at all, but you can look
to see your overall quota here.
The usage forecasts and usage trends. In
addition, there are tabs up at the
top. We have the data usage report,
but the failures report can be extremely
handy and determining why messages aren't
going out. And
we did some traffic through it, very
little, right, Just testing and stuff
like that. But as you can see,
just just tested. Fantastic. Yeah, just
nothing in the past seven days.
Then please click on the Show your
support at the top.
And then she's that one for the last
30 days as well. So in this, we
can go ahead and click and get more
details on those failures. And,
and yeah, you can click on the
individual viewer users and it will tell
you why it failed, policy violations,
filterings or delivery failures, which is
typically that preceding side. So this
can be a very useful console as
well for determining why messages aren't
going out.
Let's jump over to Relay user management,
please. And we, I'm sure you know about
this already if you send text messages
out, but this is where we can create and
modify Relay because this is more for
everybody else on the call. Let's go
ahead and walk through creating an
additional test relay user. So First
off, that name is going to
be unique to your organization.
You can add in contacts, These are
people who will be emailed in the
event of critical issues and so that
other admins of this product can see
who to contact in the event of
non deliveries. This is where you would
most likely want to put in.
The business owners of the applications
that are utilized in each individual
relay user. I
do highly recommend creating as many tags
as you need for each individual or
relay user. Tags are going to be
used in currently the reporting so that
you can look at different areas of
traffic, you can assign tags for specific
applications, things like that. In
addition as I mentioned. Moving forward,
tags are going to be used for
security purposes to allow the.
Other Christians and can be reply.
Sorry, apply other restrictions. So First
off at the top we have
the username and address combinations, or
I should just say e-mail address
combinations. So it's going to be
the the header from. I'm not
saying that's the rewrite we went down.
One right here is going to be
the the from address and then the
header from. So the from address is
the envelope sender and you can put
in wild cards here. So for example,
you could put in asterisk@tdbank.com.
Her* at* Scotch ebank.com however
you want to choose that.
And I'm assuming that we could use
supplements, right? Like absolutely. And
you can Click to see what the current
cloud domains are for your organization.
If you click on view verified domains,
that will show it on the right hand side.
Yeah, yeah. We just had your PCI E
environment there for now.
And you can just do a like a copy and
paste from the mail from and put it in
the header from.
There are scenarios where you may want
those to be different. Generally we
recommend they be the same for
authentication purposes. So this would
just be just to be clear, this
one will restrict the sending to just
this. Correct this suddenly
yeah so in in fact you can restrict it
further if you wanted to put an address
in so if you put in no reply at
it could only go out with no reply at
you're restricting how those application
owners can send traffic so this is going
to be a big feature for us because we.
Who wants to do that? We
have going forward, we're going to
ask the land of businesses to
use statistics, sample means or if
not specific e-mail addresses and be
limited to just those right and
restrict from sending to and from.
If he does.
And this is going to be. Super
important when it comes to vendors.
Remain through, through, through, right?
Absolutely. Yeah. Specific addresses and
domains. Exactly. Exactly. So this is
the thing. So that doesn't match.
Did he get a bounce or
what exactly did he get?
You are sensational layer doesn't even
accept the traffic. You would get a
failure it it wouldn't even go to your
SER pod for outbound delivery. OK.
It would probably say the exact
error message would probably be local
policy violation and it would be
a 500 error message. That internal
recipient check box. It basically says
the recipients, all of them must
match the domains listed here and.
You can add in multiple addresses, but
that check box basically says we don't
want this to go out to the Internet. We
want this to stay on the domains that are
used in the mail from addressing header
from. So generally you don't want that
check box check off because the whole
point of this product is to legitimize to
less educate your e-mail. Going out to
the Internet? Yep. If you do have
multiple Sr. clusters you can select. In
this case we only have one SCR
cluster per account, so for your PE
account you only have one.
The IP's and CIR's are the
IP addresses or IP address ranges
that would be allowed to connect
to this authentication layer using this
relay. So sorry, then can we,
can we go back for a
second? Yeah, absolutely. So for the
cluster. ER right. You mentioned that
you can have multiple clusters per
fob. Right. In
this case, you currently have one proof
point hosted classes. That's the last in
the pipeline for SER. For the on
Prem MFA's you can absolutely have as
many clusters as you need. But for
this we only have, we can only
have one, so we cannot have two.
SCR clusters that provides two different
functionalities. You could you just have
not licensed those yet that would be
between you and your account team, but
you could certainly say, hey, you know
what, we want to complete these separate
Sr. cluster to do different filtering
into only send to trusted vendors and
then you could have your original. I'm
sending just more of a mass or bulk
emails. And
the and the.
Total throughput, it's still coming
coming from the same market no
matter how many HR clusters you
have. I believe so, but I'm
not sure. OK. So you're essentially
right, Daniel, right? Yeah. And I
know what our plan is to
have separate. Your environment or
perhaps and for UMP and then for
you know the associated P environments
and that's something that we've built
into the quote structure. We can
certainly review with you as needed on
that call that we've got next Wednesday,
but that's what we've accounted for
today. He was appreciative.
Don't change anything. I just I would
just give you the fact that that that
that mentioned that you could have moved
the ones. Now we're just trying to
understand the key scenario for for
having multiple clusters, right? That's
OK. Just wanted to confirm that you like
a single management interface for the.
The surgeon, yes.
Admin.console@startupproofpoint.com is on
a per quote UN quote customer basis.
So in this case, let's just say
that you decided to add an additional
proof we hosted SER cluster for PCE.
You would be able to select which
cluster you wanted that final outbound
delivery to go through.
So one more question before we
move to the IPS and Cidrs
in regards to in general recipient,
you said if I want to
force my application to only send
emails. Relay emails to internal
disappearance. I would check that check
mark so it ensures it doesn't go out
and it's only limited to what is defined
in the mail from address, right? Correct.
It would only be able to go to
the domain to find in the mail from,
no in the mail from address. Only
to find one domain. What if the
application is sending emails to multiple
internal domains? Is that a? Is that?
Is that a setup that can be
done within this relay user record? Or
does that require multiple of these So
you can add additional addresses here?
But there will only ever be one mail
from address.
Yes, that is correct. So there is
all there is there, all there is
only. OK, fair enough. So if I
check that check mark, it's going to
limit the functionality to that whatever
domain is specified in mail from address,
correct?Now if there are more,
if the e-mail is being sent to multiple
internal domains, what happens to the all
the other emails? They're going to get
bounced back or I believe it wouldn't
even accept the the e-mail.
OK. And if he wants to set up
something like that so that an
application can send, let's say, to two
internal domains.
Is that a? Is that a
possibility you would just leave that
checkbox unchecked?
And hope that they don't send
emails out right through Internet. If
you did want to further filter
them, you could do so on
on the actual SER cluster, the
SPR_hosted cluster, you could put in
filtering rules just like the normal
you know. Ohh, I'm sending out. OK,
OK, thank you. Can just drop them
there. Yeah, thank you.
The IPCC IDR again, that is
where you can restrict who can
use this relay user. So for
example, if you put in whatever
IP range your VPN uses, only
things coming from that IP range
can utilize this relay user.
Anybody else that tries to connect is
going to get an immediate failure.
Yeah, so if you tried to connect
with like 137 dot something, you would
get in immediate failure, wouldn't even
accept the connection.
Yeah. Again, this is going to be very
useful for vendors. So we tie them to a
youthful assistant domain and a specific
IP address. Not so much for
the internal traffic, right?
Down further is the size restrictions
on any emails this relay user
is allowed to send. So notice
right now Max message size 5
megabytes.
Overall, using a relay user, you are
limited to 50 megabytes and then using
our API connections, which we do have
documented for a few popular vendors
right now with Salesforce Work Day and
a few others, you're limited to 150
megabytes and then further. There are
rate limits down below.
If you don't put any values in those,
they are not limited in those 24 hour or
one hour time periods.
I learned English for this. Yeah,
yes I would use caution both
applying a limit and not. Just
as an example, we had an
early SER customer where one of
their developers accidentally put in a
loop in their code and they
used up. Almost half of their overall
allotment in one day because they were
just constantly sending out massive
amounts of emails to the Internet and
didn't realize it.
Um, so limits are good
for that, I'll give you
that, but.
Is there some type of notification, Is
there some type of an alert that is being
triggered when something like this, it's,
it's happening because limits are good,
don't get me wrong. It's just going to
take longer to spread the pain, right?
Hopefully in the meantime, somebody is
going to, is going to, is going to see
it. Fix it. But I mean, you
know, instead of using, you know, in
the case that you mentioned half the
afternoon time in in in one day,
you could use increased in three days,
right? Yes. So the relay user API
does have notifications where it can
notify you when certain thresholds.
OK, OK.
So that is so we can pull
that data from from from from there.
Yes, OK. What about, what about the
reports that you were showing us where
it could show you what kind of
failures you have in the outbound
traffic? Could that identify issues like
this?Absolutely, it will show you usage
trends. OK, yeah, but that
requires somebody to look at those,
right? Yeah, that's my, that's the point
that I'm trying. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
If nobody's looking at those and nobody
knows about it, yes, we have limits
that's going to spread the pain over
three days instead of one day. But again,
unless somebody gets certified and.
Somebody that could be looking at this,
it's it's, it's a slope that things start
right, but not much.
OK. So at
the very bottom, we have
unsubscribed management. If you start
an unsubscribe and then yeah,
OK. So how quickly can
for example, how quickly you
turn around then if we've
already consumed up the all
of the. Allotted amount, I'll
quickly can you turn around
adding additional um.
Capacity to us, where does that turn
around for example, I don't know what
the turn around is much will alleviate
your concern. It requires somebody from
your sales team to manually come in
to the Sr. portal or talk to
our back end operations to actually stop
your outbound mail flow. If you exceed
the allotted limit, we do not have
an automated shutoff. We understand the
necessity and use cases where outbound
e-mail needs to go out and sometimes
you might go over that allotment, but
there is no automatic hard cap where
it just shuts down your ability to
send emails. OK, so it's not like so
again, we're not.
We, it won't automatically turn off.
It'll still function, but most likely
we'll get a call from, you
know, the account managers just saying,
hey, you gotta pay up something
up. OK, Thanks. Yeah, it's a
great question. Yeah, perfect. And then
he unsubscribed. Down at the bottom,
this will basically if it sees its
height to an unsubscribed list, it will
be adding headers to any outbound e-mail.
Those headers are utilized by popular
e-mail clients where you can just click
unsubscribe for example in Gmail or
Google Workspace and Notification. You
know will come back and that user
will be added to that unsubscribe list.
Meaning when sending through this relay
user, that user's e-mail will be stripped
for any outbound future emails.
So that's the capital company that that's
capital compliance, yes. And and there
are going to be additional
functionalities that you unsubscribe
management moving forward. I do know they
are working on a URL embedded within the
e-mail that can be clicked as well. Not
quite here yet, but we do comply.
It's just as Example and spam Act
in the United States or Castle compliance
in Canada. Sorry,
thank you. Run that by me one
more time. So you have a you
create this unsubscribe list right there.
Subscribe list, unsubscribe. This is
composed of what users e-mail addresses
right? External e-mail address. OK.
So I sent an e-mail to
to jed@gmail.com, right? He clicks. I
don't want his emails.
Yeah, you know that his e-mail address
is added to the list when the
relay user goes. If it's that e-mail
as a recipient on any future mailings,
it will strip that e-mail out of
the two or CC or BCC or
wherever he is in it.
That's, uh, that's, umm.
For relay user, right? Yes.
However multiple relay users can
share the same unsubscribe.
I'm just thinking we don't want to share
it baby, right?
So that has the ability to
feed into like an existing database
that we might have right with
APIs. We do. We
actually do. We do have a Capacity Castle
compliant database where end users are
told that they can do it. It's just
not really integrated with what we do.
It's that URL that you attach in the
header and we do have a Catholic
compliance. It's just that it's not an
automated process. Also
go to website.
I know what you're saying right now from
an application perspective though, each
individual LED's or individual sender
right now I'm talking about right now is
right now, of course we don't have, we
don't have it all. But The thing is
again, a lot of the our applications are
not the compliant like or. External
sending. So I guess The thing
is it's more of a future
enhancement for us to talk to
the people who own castle to
encourage them to manage it. Now
I guess the other question is,
is that your database or this
when when somebody. Um, goes in,
unsubscribes it, it you place it
in a proof point area, right?
And then our application would have
to call that area to pull
out it from our main list,
right? Or and vice versa in
the way that. It would, uh,
feed into like the ultimate database.
Yes. And there is an API for that
as well. We have an unsubscribe API where
you can read and write to the point
list so that it can be synchronized with
some sort of masculist underside. OK. And
once the user gets onto that unsubscribe
list, let's say Jeff Flakes and subscribe
and then. Ohh shoot, I didn't mean to.
No what?What's
the undo option? That's a
good question. I am not
sure. OK. Because it's, it's
OK if you end up in the list, but I mean,
you know, some at some point in time you
might wanna get off actually for whatever
reason, right, Right. That
is probably where the API would come
into play where you know they could
resubscribe on on the key bank side
and then your masculist could using the
API update the proof point list and
I guess again it would be to
customize it. So for example I might
not want. Females from like
Arshad, but I want the communal.
That would be something I had.
I would have to customize through
the API right? Yes, OK.
So then, if you don't mind, can we
put this on the on the list of
things that that we can check back on
to see how that process works from being
removed from an unsubscribed list?
I'm I'm not sure what you mean how
exactly it works to be removed. Yes yes
that's what I meant. I'm on the
Proofpoint side. We send out an
unsubscribe header and then it would be
up to the individual e-mail client to
offer an unsubscribe through that. I know
Gmail already has it and it's optional.
In Outlook, so we're talking about,
you know, 90 something percent of
the world's e-mail clients. Moving
forward we will have an unsubscribed
URL option. However, when you unsubscribe
header is activated, it will add
that e-mail address to the list
local on. SER and then you
can do whatever you need to do
via the API. But what I was
asking is once you're on the list,
how do you get off the unsubscribed
list? It would be API calls from
your central database. So
you you have the option to remove it
from there. Yes, it is there an option
to create the list but not action on
it? Yeah.
You can create everything here and it's
not going to do anything because it's
going to be blank.
No no no no. I mean
when a user clicks on the
unsubscribe right? Can the system just
generate a list and provide it
to maybe our back end to
update or something on their life
rather than immediate action if the
user activates the unsubscribe?Their
their e-mail address is added to whatever
unsubscribed list is associated with the
relay user that sent that e-mail out, and
that is essentially like a gatekeeper or
a goalie. It will prevent emails from
going from that relay user to that user.
It would be a different error message
when a user tries to send an
e-mail to a user that 800 subscribers.
Is it something? OK, so it's something
that then we see over there and
if they're watching the logs, yes, OK,
fair enough. I believe it's also
available in the shelters report.
Yeah, I'm more concerned about the, you
know, getting them getting a notification
back when the e-mail is not delivered for
whatever reason. They will see the reason
for why it's it's not being sent as
opposed to reach back to us for us to
go and and and do it right. It would
be like kind of like a. With
manage uh. Thing for, for, for
the, for the, for the business, right,
For the, yeah, yeah, OK.
Let's go ahead and click on next
so that we can see the the
next options here. Last we get to
the alias. This alias, if you decide
to type one in, must be globally
unique, IE this has to be unique
across all three-point customers. This is
the username. That is part of the
username password combination that
essentially makes up a relationship.
If you were to click save right now,
it would create a GUID as an alias
for you and it would generate a random
12 character password. It
would be up to you to disseminate that
username and password to whatever
application owners need to use this data
user. In fact, when you click on save
on the next screen you can click a
download where you can copy out all of
the information for that.
So do we want to do this
as opposed to keep guessing if it
has to be unique across? Ohh, yeah,
absolutely. I I recommend always letting
us still to go in. This would
be for a scenario where if you
had some, you know, mainframe app coded
in 1988 that couldn't. Use
8 characters or less. You could
come up with some globally unique
8 character username so that legacy
application could send out. So whenever
I stop thinking typing something in
here. He will start
checking against a list when I when I
click save or how is that going to work?
Yes, it will look across the entire
global list of all different customers.
However, we have been strongly
recommending using the GUID. So you made
it obviously if they come up with
something. And strongly recommend using
do it for all of our customers. You may
be may be able to decide something in
right now. I would bet if you type in
test it probably wouldn't work. But if
you just like test XYZ 123 maybe it would
work. He gave you
like playing test please. Tried
to claim it. No, but
to be honest with you that I like that
idea of that, of that random guy. Right.
Yeah. Because that's what we want. Yeah,
right. It's it's it's not something that.
Yeah, but I still want to try to claim
test, please. There you go. There you go.
Safe No, you cannot do so. OK,
it's like a popular post on social
media and somebody typing in first.
That's the first comment exactly no, but
this is really good. I like that
option of grid and even when I
created mine like initially I like that
idea that. You know, it's a, it's a
big long number that cannot be like, you
really have to type it in and you have to
go in the competition with the password
and all that stuff, right? Yeah, for
sure, yeah.
So here we can and and you can
change that password. My personal habit
over the last couple of years I do
19 characters because I have run across
some Internet sites that have a 20
character limit, but 19 seems to be a
pretty good sweet spot between easily
crackable. The group force and getting
into the, you know, many, many years
by reports level, Yeah.
OK. And OK, so there's a time
frame for this. This is good.
So if I set up three months,
what's going to happen after three
months? And again, coming back to this,
Yeah, yeah. That password will no longer
be usable by this relay user. And
you can create a new password and
have overlap time, meaning the new
password. The old one both worked for one
week. And that allows you to get that
password to the application owners.
About from a sender perspective, they
gonna get some type of an error message
saying that the password expired, the
login is not current anymore or something
along those lines. I believe it's just
invalid authentication. OK, but that's
good enough because they will know what
internal competition issue, yes, OK.
Is there?
Any reports that will give us?
Um, the passwords that are
coming close to.
I don't think we're going to use the.
I don't necessarily think that we're
going to use the password expiration,
maybe one, maybe one, but this is
available in the Relay user API. OK, so
in there you can see each users probably
how much longer it hasn't been the end
of time or that's correct. OK, OK,
so then just as an example, so I've
played around with this API a little bit
before. What I did is I set up some
PowerShell function, one function I said,
hey, this all of the relay users for the
entire quote UN quote customer and it
listed them out. And then you could put
that list into a variable and say. For
each item in this variable, go ahead and
give me the password expiration. Yeah,
yeah, yeah. No, that makes sense.
And if we tie this in with
with the with the automated process there
was they will notify, you know, a
group of individuals that are responsible
for that application that's going to work
fantastic there. Exactly. And then we can
set this up for 12 months and
in a way then. This would be
all about this patient that, that, that,
that applications could use and it's to
be used, yes.
And that is called month mark. Using the
API you can create a new password and
again you can have an overlap. Where the
new and the old both are are valid
at the same time. OK.
I don't know how we're going to use this,
but but it's, it's good that it's here,
right?
Um, is there any type
of report that that that
can give us unused usernames?
It's your user names so I create so
we created like 1010 users but a year
down the road we want to know is
are they still in use?
I can click on every single one of them
and then just save them if they're still
in use, which works fine for like, you
know, 100 and we have thousands. That's
going to be hard.
Yeah, give me a second. I'm looking at
our relay user API to see.
If that is an option is
that would be fantastic.
That's one of the things that we're
lacking right now. We're lacking the,
the, the ability to look up if, if
an IP or an application or a user
is still still using or still consuming
the current service, right, right. Unless
you go 1 by 1, which again, we
have over 8000 IPS right now, you know?
Umm, I don't know basis, right? But you
can imagine that this happened about
going through all the steps, right? So
that's why I'm just wondering if if it's
an easy way that we'll be looking around
something or query something that would
give us that information. That would be
fantastic.
Can you utilize the tax to
pull reports on?
Yes. Ohh,
yeah.
If anything, that.
Is not using that tag. See how
many emails? If it's zero, then it's
not if. Finger or
something with those API's. So those are
the those API's are full days, right?
Uh, they, they are recognized.
OK, Yeah. So I could
build something for those. Yeah.
Nothing stopping us from from how to
listen until next Tuesday when we meet
again. I'll start playing those CPA's to
see see what we can get out of this.
There we go. Make sure you grab this out
of the zoom shots.
That is the API link for the reporting
API.
And then under usage trend we
could do get relay users usage
data.
OK, so you OK I see what you say. So
you can get the user data based on the
user and if it's zero then you know it's
not use correct? Is there a time frame
that you can specify?
I believe so. Um.
OK.
I'm just looking right now.
Yes, it will. Uh, you can submit dates as
part of the POST request.
OK, awesome.
Let me give you just quickly just to just
to follow up on that, but how long are
the logs around for?And
after 30 days, 30 days, OK, which is
why we recommend shipping the logs to a
stem like like Splunk.
OK.
So for sure, we're gonna do, we're gonna
shoot the last talk.
We already have. The
people working on that to, to, to.
Start configuration, yes.
Alright. So
here is the beginning of a Webber
Request cost API and you can see
dates at the very bottom of that
so you can list updates. In this
case it would give you everything in
the 24 hour period on November 1st,
2023.
Yeah, yeah, that makes sense.
I believe we are at time for today, time
for us when we're having fun here.
Absolutely.
Any questions before we drop off?
No, I think we're good to that.
Excellent. No, but thanks for the
session. It was great. You are most
welcome. I hope you all had a happy
Canadian Independence Day and I will be
celebrating dinner and when this coming
Saturday I wake up. More propane for my
grill and I got some sparklers.
Enjoy that then. Thank you so
much. OK, go bye bye.